Hall, Kermit; Papers ua902.070
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Kermit Hall Papers
1956-2006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua902.070
8.19 cubic ft.
Personal papers of former University at Albany President Kermit Hall, who passed away suddenly in 2006.
Collection X
Biographical / Historical
Kermit Lance Hall was born on August 31, 1944 in Akron, Ohio. Hall served in the Vietnam War from 1967-1969 and then earned a bachelor's degree from the University of Akron, a master's degree from Syracuse University in 1967, and a Ph.D from the University of Minnesota in 1972. Hall also recieved a MSL from Yale Law School in 1980. He was a recognized scholar and expert on legal history and the Supreme Court and wrote extensively on the development of federal and state courts. In 1979, as a scholar at Wayne State University, Hall published his first book, The Politics of Justice: Lower Federal Judicial Selection and the Second Party System, 1829-61.
On December 29, 2004, Hall was named the 17th president of the University at Albany, State University of New York. Prior to his appointment at Albany, Hall held academic and administrative positions at Vanderbilt University (1972-1976), University of Florida (1981-1992), University of Tulsa (1992-1994), before landing at Ohio State University in 1994 as Dean of the College of Humanities from 1994-1999, and as Executive Dean and a professor of History and Law of the College of Arts and Sciences (1996-99). From 1999-2001 he was the Provost and Vice President for academic affairs and a professor of History at North Carolina State University before becoming President and professor of History at Utah State University until 2005.
Hall was also known for his various publications about the American law and the judicial branch. His works granted him various awards including grants from the National Endowment for Humanities, the American Bar Association, and the James Madison Award from the American Library Association. While he worked on many long term publications concerning the Supreme Court and legal history, a significant amount of his research was dedicated to The New York Times v Sullivan, a case that originated in Alabama and concerned libel and freedom of the press. Beyond the First Amendment implications, Hall's research and writings on this case explored the racial tensions and civil rights coverage in Alabama that was intertwined with the court's proceedings at the time.
In 1992, President Bill Clinton appointed Hall to the five member Assassination Records Review Board to review and approve the release of public documents related to the assassination of President John F. Kennedy. Hall served as board member for numerous organizations relating to higher education, including the American Council on Eduction, the National Association of State University and Land Grant Colleges, the International Student Exchange Program, the NCAA Presidential Task Force on the Future of Intercollegiate Athletics, and the Research Foundation of the State University of New York. He was formerly a member of the board of the Research Triangle Institute, one of the nation's most succesful private research enterprises. Hall held fellowships and grants from the National Endowment for the Humanities, the National Science Foundation, the American Council of Learned Societies, the American Bar Foundation, and the Fulbright Education Foundation.
Hall died on August 13, 2006 in South Carolina and was survived by his wife Phyllis.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Kermit Hall's personal papers.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically into four series as follows:
1: New York Times v Sullivan, 1956-2004, undated 2: Assassination Records Review Board, 1963-2004, undated 3: Essays and Publications, 1983-2005, undated 4: UAlbany Talks and Presentations, 2004-2006, undated
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Phyllis Hall donated materials to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2007.
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Scope and Contents
Includes much of the materials housed in Kermit Hall's office after his death. Includes publications, manuscripts, research files on New York Times Co. v. Sullivan, records from the Assassination Records Review Board, and speeches given while President of UAlbany.
UAlbany Faculty & Alumni Papers; Hall, Kermit L., 1944-2006; History--Study and teaching.; Law (discipline); Research (documents); Research Notes; Research; United States. Supreme Court.; Lectures.; News Clippings; Manuscripts for publication; Constitution; Civil Rights; Race relations; assassinations
- New York Times v. Sullivan, 1956-2004; 1; 3 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains research material including interview transcripts, news clippings, manuscript drafts, and research articles
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically
  - Alabama Court Research, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brennan, Justice William NY Times, 1976; 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bibliography, 1961-1965; 1980; 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biographies/General, 1963; 1977; 1986; 1988-1989; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cases: Miscellaneous/Alabama, 1957; 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Case Summary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights, Defamation, and the South, 1989; 2003; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Commentary on Press Privacy and Malice: Reflections on NYT v Sullivan, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Draft: Lies, Lies, Lies, A Place in Time, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Draft: Lies, Lies, Lies: The Origins of NY Times Co. v. Sullivan, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Draft: NY Times v. Sullivan and its Times, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Embry Interview, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Federalism: '87 and Beyond/ A Confrontation: New York Times v. Sullivan, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Gray Interview, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Handwritten Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hearings: NYT vs Sullivan, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hopkins, W Wat: Inside the U.S. Supreme Court Decision-Making in New York Times Co. v. Sullivan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Impact of Sullivan: Law Review Literature Hustler Mag v. Falwell, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Impact of Sullivan: Law Review Literature General, 1965; 1981-1988; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Impact of Sullivan: Law Review Literature Philadelphia News v. Hepps, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Impact of Sullivan: Law Review Literature Rosenblatt v. Baer, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Impact of Sullivan: Cases, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Interview Forms/Releases, 1898-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Interviews: Miscellaneous, 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Jenkins Interview, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Jones, Judge Walter B. Microfilm Research, 1960; 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Judge Brennan Papers, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Justice Brennan and Cultural History: Hall Article, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Justice Brennan, Justice Harlan, and NYT v. Sullivan, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - King v. Mister Maestro, Inc., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Labor at the Ballot Box: Unions in Alabama Politics from Franklin Roosevelt to George Wallace, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lecture by Hall: The Constitutional Lessons of the Little Rock Crisis, The Little Rock Conference, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lecture by Other: Historical Origins of NY Times v. Sullivan, Hawaii International Conference, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Letters: Judge Eric Embry, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Letter to J. Mills Thornton from Hall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Letter to Nancy Nielson from Hall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Letter to Roland Nachman Jr from Hall, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Libel Cases Alabama, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Libel Cases NY Times, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Libel Law Review Literature Histories, Definitions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Libel/Malice Cases, General, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Libel Press Coverage, Alabama, 1960-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lies, Lies, Lies, the Origins of New York Times Co. V. Sullivan, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - McDonald Interview, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1977; 1983; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Montgomery Bus Boycott Glennon Article, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New York Times v. Sullivan and its Times Speech, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - NYT Coverage of Alabama Racial Tensions, 1963; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NYT v. Sullivan and its Times, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYT v. Sullivan Case Notes, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NYT v. Sullivan Reconsidered, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Ochs, Adolph, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Oral Interview Releases, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Patterson Interview, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Petition for Writ of Certiorari, Times v. Sullivan, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Public Officials and Libel: In Defense of NYT v. Sullivan, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Race Relations Alabama, General New York Times 1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Race Relations, Alabama General NY Times 1961 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Race Relations, Alabama General NY Times 1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Race Relations, Alabama General NY Times 1963 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Race Relations, Alabama General NY Times 1964 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Race Relations, Freedom Rides NY Times 1961 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Race Relations, Freedom Rides NY Times 1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Race Relations, State Cases, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Race Relations, Supreme Court Cases, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Reprints by Hall: Cultural History and the First Amendment, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Reprints by Hall: Legal Lore, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Reprints by Other: Anthony Lewis, Make No Law, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Reprints by Other: Challenge and Response in the Montgomery Bus Boycott, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Reprints by Other: Rediscovering Florida's Common Law Defenses to Libel and Slander, 1981; 1990 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Research Material, M. Roland Nachman Jr, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Research Material, News Clipping and Obituaries, 1960-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Response to Professor Franklin, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Rogers Interview, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Salisbury Atlanta Constitution, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Salisbury Cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Salisbury Montgomery Advertiser, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Salisbury NY Times, Atlanta Constitution, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Salisbury NY Times 1962 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Salisbury NY Times 1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Scintilla of Evidence Rule, 1979; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Shuttlesworth Interview, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Statistical Information, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sullivan Alabama Case, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Sullivan Archives, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sullivan Atlanta Constitution, 1960-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Sullivan, Commissioner L.B., 1960; 1964; 1967; 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Sullivan Montgomery Advertiser 1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Sullivan Montgomery Advertiser 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Sullivan NY Times 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sullivan NY Times 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Sullivan NY Times 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Sullivan NY Times 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Supreme Court Douglas Papers, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Supreme Court General, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Transcript, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Transcript: Times v. Sullivan pp. 1/486, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Transcript: Times v. Sullivan pp. 487/998, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Transcript: Times v. Sullivan pp. 999/1745, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Transcript: Times v. Sullivan pp. 1835/2243 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Assassination Records Review Board, 1963-2004; 2; 1.96 cubic ft.
  This series contains board meeting notes, research documents, nomination materials and news clippings.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Board information: Chronology, 1992; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board Information: Federal Documents, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board Information Packet, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board Information: Press Release, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Information: Release Advisory, 1995; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Depatment of State Briefing, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Final Report of the Assassination Records Review Board, 1998 (Oversize 1)
  - Germaine Topics of Interest: The John F. Kennedy Assassination, 1997 (A/v box 1, Video-tape 1)
  - Hearings, Dallas, TX, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - JFK Assassination Documents, 1993; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - JFK Library Files, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - LBJ Library, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lecture by Hall, Kennedy Assassination Conspiracy Dinner and Presidential Lecture, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lecture by Hall, National Association of Government Archives and Records Administrators Luncheon, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, ARRB, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, ARRB Briefing Book Boston, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Meetings, ARRB Briefing Book Washington, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, ARRB January, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meetings, ARRB November, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Meetings, ARRB Public Meeting Boston, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Meetings, ARRB Washington, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Meetings, January ARRB Washington, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - News Clippings January/June, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - News Clippings January/May, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - News Clippings June/August, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings March/November, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings September/November, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings September/December, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Nomination Material, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Nomination Material White House Documents, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Report ARRB Fiscal Year, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Report: Selected Released Documents, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Research Material: ARRB Reference Manual and Source Book, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Research Material: CIA Historical Review Program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Research Material: Documents Relating to Subpoena for Jim Garrison Paper, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Research Material: FBI and CIA Documents (1 of 3), 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Research Material: FBI and CIA Documents (2 of 3), 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Research Material: FBI and CIA Documents (3 of 3), 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Research Material: Hall's Notes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Research Material: Information from Switzerland, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Research Material: JFK Assassination FAQ, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Research Material: Hall's Kennedy Files (1 of 2), 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Research Material: Hall's Kennedy Files (2 of 2), 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Research Material: JFK Research Material, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Research Material: Joseph Backes Letter, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Research Material: The Kennedy Assassination, 1995-2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Research Material: Photos, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Research Material: Lee Harvey Oswald, the CIA, and Mexico, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Research Material: Moscow, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Research Material: NSA Documents, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Research Material: NSA and Secret Service Documents, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Research Material: Records Information, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Research Material: Rusty Wilson Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Research Material: Slides/Transparency (1 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Research Material: Slides/Transparency (2 of 2), Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Research Material: South Texas Law Review, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Research Material: Subpoena for Jim Garrison Papers, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Research Material: Warren Report, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - WGN Radio, Chicago, 1996 (A/v box 1, Cassette 1)
- Essays and Publications, 1983-2005; 3; 1.4 cubic ft.
  This series contains the majority of Hall's major publications, and sometimes includes correspondences with the editor and draft revisions along with the published material
  - Academic Realities, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amending the Constitution, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Bar Foundation Research Journal, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Articles Authored by KLH, for Reproduction, 1984; 2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Benchmark, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Canon of American Constitutional History, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cambridge History of American Law, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Celebratory Rioting, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Changing Supreme Court, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Clinton & The Scales of Federal Justice, 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Constitutions and Rights Presentation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constitutions, the Supreme Court, and Rights, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Courage of His Convictions, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Equity in Education and the Legacy of Brown v. Board, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Federalism and Constitutional Rights, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Federal Judicial Reform and Proslavery Constitutional Theory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hacks and Derelicts Revisited, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Hall- Déjà Vu all Over Again, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Harvard Lecture, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Heed Their Rising Voices, 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - History by the Hind Leg: The Lower Federal Courts and the Past, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Election Returns (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Judiciary on Trial: State Constitutional Reform and the Rise of an Elected Judiciary, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kennedy Talk, 1960; 1963; 1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Law and the Midwest, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Legal Culture of the Great Plains, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Magic Mirror, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Magic Mirror Revisions, 1992-1994; 1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Magic Mirror (Talk), Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Marquette Law Review, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mostly Anchor and Little Sail, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - New York Times v. Sullivan and its Times: Hall Address, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Notes, 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - NYT v Sullivan Essays, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Of Floors and Ceilings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Open Secrets Lecture, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Path Not Taken, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Political Power and Constitutional Legitimacy, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Power of Comparison in Teaching about Constitutionalism, Law, and Democracy, 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Progressive Reform and the Decline of Democratic Accountability, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Reputation of James Wilson Drafts, 2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Route to Hell Retraced, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Supreme Court and Judicial Review, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Supreme Court Presentations, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Supreme Court, Judicial Review, and the Nation Building Process, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Think Things, Not Words: Judicial Review in U.S. Constitutional History, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Total Justice, Liberty, and the Rule of Law in American History, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Twenty-One Tips to Teaching About Constitution in American History, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Virulence of the National Appetite for Bogus Revelation, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- UAlbany Talks and Presentations, 2004-2006; 4; 2.1 cubic ft.
  This series contains transcripts and information about events that Hall spoke at while President of UAlbany, including commencements, awards and recognition ceremonies, and campus community events.
  - 15th Anniversary of Committee on University and Community Relations, 2006 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 19th Annual Spellman Achievement Awards, 2005 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 20th Annual Spellman Achievement Awards, 2006 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1844 Club Reception, 2005 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Bill of Rights, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Academic Bill of Rights, 2006 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - All-Alumni Luncheon, 2006 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albany High School-UAlbany Alliance for Young Talents Collaborates to Support At-Risk AHS Students News Conference, 2006 March 21 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Marketing Association: "How a Few Cows Turned into an Utter Success", 2005 November 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Americans for Informed Democracy, 2006 April 25 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Author Reading & Book Signing Exhibit Opening-University Libraries, 2005 May 13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - BHER: Competitiveness of Metro Areas & What Tech Valley Can Do with Bruce Katz, 2005 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BHER: Innovation in Tech Valley: Leadership with Bruce Katz, 2005 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Big Purple Growl & Ferocious Feast, 2006 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Brian Lamb Event, 2005 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CASDA Scholars' Recognition Dinner, 2006 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Capital Region CPAs and Bankers, 2005 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Celebrating the Publication of the Oxford Companion to the Supreme Court 2nd Edition, 2005 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Center for Autism 2nd Annual Wine & Food Tasting Event, 2005 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Center for Elimination of Minority Health Disparities, 2005 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Characteristics of a Great Public University Overhead, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Citizen Laureate Awards Dinner, 2005 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Dinner, 2006 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Commencement-161st Graduate Ceremony, 2005 May 14 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Commencement-162nd Graduate Ceremony, 2006 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Commencement-162nd Undergraduate Ceremony, 2006 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Council for Economic Outreach Breakfast, 2005 March 4 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Council for Economic Outreach Breakfast, 2006 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Council for Economic Outreach-CEO Breakfast, 2005 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Counsel's Office Meeting JFK Presentation, 2005 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - CSEA Archives to UAlbany Grenander Collection, 2005 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - D'Andrea, Frank Welcome Reception, 2005 September 30 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - December Commencement, 2005 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Delmar Humanities Institute of Lifelong Learning, 2006 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Distinguished Professor Lecture: Dr. Lance F. Bosart, 2005 March 30 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Donation of Joseph Persico Papers, 2006 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - E.J. Corey Honorary Degree Convocation, 2005 April 25 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Excellence Awards, 2006 May 11 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Excellence Awards Program, 2005 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes-Spring, 2005 April 27 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Fall Faculty Meeting, 2005 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - First Niagara Bank Gift Presentation Gen*NY*Sis Center for Excellence, 2006 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Friends Exhibit, 2006 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Gen*NY*Sis Center for Excellence in Cancer Genomics Opening, 2005 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Gen*NY*Sis Media Tour & Check Presentation, 2005 July 26 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Giants Pre-practice Reception, 2005 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 46)